Raymond Zeaiter

Junior Full Stack Web Developer

SUMMARY

Motivated junior full-stack web developer who is seeking the start of a new career in the IT industry. Spent almost a decade prior to this new journey as a teacher, and now is seeking to deploy his new skills in innovating and exciting ways.

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Free Duck Finder

Live Site: https://freeduckfinder.online

React, TailwindCSS, Node.js, MongoDB, APIs

Web application that allows users to find and submit local duck ponds. Uses a custom API hoisted on Heroku to store and retrieve location data.

Personal Portfolio

Live Site: https://raymond-zeaiter.au

React, TailwindCSS

Personal portfolio website built using React and styled with TailwindCSS

Other Projects: Pokémon-themed Slot Machine, Advice Generator app using API, Weight Tracking app

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer

February 2022 — Present

Created full stack responsive web applications and static websites for different clients using best practices.

Actual Client - Clair De Lune Trio

Live Site: https://clairdelunetrio-sydney.netlify.app/

· React, TailwindCSS

Fully responsive website for a local Sydney band. Features a built in music player.

High School Teacher

April 2015 — December 2021

Worked across a number of schools teaching Mathematics, History and Geography. During my tenure I also took on middle-management roles as a Year Coordinator, managing staff and communicating with parents.

CONTACT

(+61) 423 688 274

ray.z@live.com.au

raymond-zeaiter.au

github.com/king-oldmate

linkedin.com/in/raymond-zeaiter

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React

Node.js

MongoDB

OOP

Web Accessibility

EDUCATION

University of Notre Dame, Sydney

2014 - 2015

Australian Catholic University

2008 - 2011